Hello Evan, today we will talk
about ICICI Lord's Q3 numbers.
All the figures are given in lakhs, I will
tell it in crores. So first of all let
us talk about its total income. If we look at it, it was Rs
4300 crore, from there it is increasing to Rs
5000 crore on yearly basis. If we
look at it quarterly, it was around Rs 49 crore, from there it is
decreasing a little to Rs 5000 crore. So if we
look at it on yearly basis, there is a good jump
in its net income, but on quarterly basis a
slight flat decline is being seen. If
we look at its total expenses, it was Rs
4000 crore, from there it increased to Rs
4500 crore. If we look at it quarterly, it was Rs
4400 crore, from there it increased to Rs
4500 crore yearly. Well, if we look at it quarterly,
its expenses have increased, but
on its quarterly basis a slight flat
decline was seen in its income, but
expenses are continuously  It grew well
quarterly, now let us talk about its
profit and loss after tax. If we
look at it, the profit was Rs 352 crore,
from there it has increased to Rs 431 crore, if
seen on quarterly basis, it was Rs 577 crore,
from there it has decreased to Rs 431 crore, so
in the quarterly there was a lot of decline in
its net profit, but on yearly basis there are
good numbers, these are the numbers
of ICICI Lord, on yearly basis there are good
numbers, but on quarterly basis there are bad
numbers for ICICI L Part,
so subscribe to the channel to watch such news, thank
you.